绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第十集
他居然没要求我们打卡  真令人惊讶
Surprised he doesn't make us do that.
狼群有严格的等级
The pack totally has a pecking order.
土狼头领  就是老大
And the head Hyena, he's the man.
其它土狼都得  舔它的屁股
All the other ones have to, like, kiss his ass.
不是夸张  是真的  太恶心了
I mean, literally. It's so gross.
它们都得去舔
They have to lick his jerk.
电视上竟然还演这个  我都没法相信
I-I-I can't believe they even showed it on TV.
要是咱们这真想搞成职业联盟那样的
Yo, if this is supposed to be all, like, Major League and all,
就该有专人来维护设备
we should have equipment maintainer guys.
还得有送水的  知道吗
And water boys. You know?
贱人  来瓶佳得乐
Yo, Gatorade me, bitch.
再找两个狗腿子
Get us a couple flunkies in here.
把咱们服侍好
Treat us right.
好了  定时为15个小时
Okay, 15 hours starts now.
你没意见的话我就开工了
I'm going to hit it, if that's cool with you.
我不明白
I don't understand.
明白什么
What?
这些数字  怎么算都对不上
These numbers, they just don't add up.
早跟你说了  那家伙压榨我们
Told you. Dude's totally boning us.
不  不是那事
No, it's not that.
是我们的产量  少了
It's our output. We're off.
少了百分之0.14
We're 0.14% off.
百分之0.14...  到底什么意思
Point one-four, that's what, like... What does that mean?
意思是我们的产量少于应有的
It means we should be netting more than we're netting.
少了多少
So how far off are we?
少到不能忽略不计了
It's not negligible.
粗略算了下  大概少了0.25到0.5磅
Ball-parking it, I'd say we're quarter to a half a pound shy.
真奇怪
That's weird.
溢出量算了吗
What about spillage?
溢出量
Spillage?
就是  不小心溅出来那些
Yeah, you know, like, just stuff gets spilled.
没溅出过任何东西
Nothing gets spilled.
或许有一点点呢
A little maybe.
没溅出过任何东西
Nothing gets spilled.
那蒸发了呢
What about evaporation?
蒸发量不会有这么大
It wouldn't account for this much.
原料暴露时间又没那么长
The materials aren't out that long.
那么  水滴呢  就像...
What about the other one? The drops, like on...
冰啤酒瓶上的那种
on that, like, cold beer.
冷凝吗
Condensation?
对
Yeah.
不可能
No.
会不会是剩下的那些渣滓
What about the crap that gets left behind,
就是  我们从桶里抠出来的粘糊糊的东西
you know, all the gunk we scrape out of the vats?
我算了  每个桶差不多有一加仑
I add up, like, a gallon each.
你算进去了吗
Did you work that in?
残留
Vestiges?
对  残留
Yeah. Vestiges.
肯定是这个
Bet that's it.
肯定就是这个了
Bet that's totally it.
怀特老师
Hey, Mr. White.
-怀特老师  -说
- Mr. White. - Huh?
你还好吧
Are you okay?
很好  怎么了
Yeah... Yeah, why?
没事
Nothing.
你不走吗
Are you coming?
好  马上
Yeah, in a minute.
好吧  明天见
All right, see you tomorrow.
该死
Shit.
你个杂种
You bastard.
狗娘养...
Son of a...
来呀
Come on, you...
来呀  来呀
Come on, come on.
狗娘养...
Son of a...
好
Okay.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
太好了
That's great.
小杂种
You little bastard.
关上门
Shut the door!
我耳朵要炸了
My ears are popping.
关上门  快
Shut the door. Move.
这感觉像在飞机似的
It's like I'm on an airplane, yo.
什么鬼东西搞的
What the hell's doing that?
正压力
Positive pressure.
正什么
Positive what?
老天  真要人命
God, friggin' kills, yo.
动动下巴  来回活动
Well, just move your jaw around. Move it around.
我动着呢  不管用
I am moving it around. It's not working.
那就打个呵欠什么的  别大惊小怪
Then just yawn or something. Stop acting like such a baby.
该死
Damn.
那什么正  正什么
W-W-What positive? Positive what?
压力  我调高了通风设备的阀值
Pressure. I've turned the ventilation up
使这里与外界产生压力差
to keep the outside out.
这里出现了"污染物"
There's been a contamination.
等下  什么
Wait. What?
喂  等一下
Whoa whoa whoa, hey, hold up.
实验室里进了东西
Something got into the lab.
我们怎么办
So what do we do?
我是说  我们
I mean, do we...
等等  等等  我们不该戴面罩吗
Wait. Wait. I mean, shouldn't we be wearing masks?
不不  不是...那种"污染物"
No, no, it's not that... that kind of contaminant.
那是什么  不危险吗
So it's, like, not dangerous?
怀特老师  我跟你说话呢
Mr. White, talk to me here.
对我们无害
Not to us particularly. No.
那是什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
这个...  是我做的
This is, uh... I made it.
那这啥"污染物"到底是什么
So exactly what kind of contaminant are we dealing with here?
一只苍蝇
A fly.
什么意思
What do you mean?
一只...  什么苍蝇
A fly, like... like what do you mean?
我说的就是苍蝇  家蝇
I mean a fly, a house fly.
就是  一只苍蝇
Like, uh, one fly?
就一只  它干了什么
Singular? What did it do?
它飞进了实验室  我要打死它
It got into the lab, and I'm trying to get it out.
行了吗  懂不懂
Okay? Understand?
没懂  哥们
No, man, not really.
我想我还是没跟上你思路
I can't say that I'm really following you here.
伙计  你把我魂都吓飞了
Dude, you scared the shit out of me.
你说污染物的时候
I mean, when you say it's contamination,
我还以为是  埃博拉病毒什么的呢
I mean, I'm thinking, like an Ebola leak or something.
埃博拉病毒
Ebola?
对  探索频道播的一种病
Yeah, it's a disease on The Discovery Channel,
能让你把肠子都拉出来
where all your intestines sort of just slip right out of your butt.
谢谢  我知道埃博拉病毒是什么
Thank you. I know what Ebola is.
你倒说说看  西非病毒怎么会
Now, tell me. What would a West-African virus
跑到我们实验室里
be doing in our lab?
你自己满屋撵苍蝇
So you're chasing around a fly,
还说我是白痴
and in your world I'm the idiot.
杰西  听着
Jesse, listen.
这只苍蝇...  任何苍蝇
This fly... any fly...
都不可以出现在我们实验室
cannot be in our lab.
它是个问题
It's... It's a problem.
它是污染物
It's a contamination,
我绝对没有用错词
and that is in no way a misuse of the word.
懂了吗
Okay?
为保证我们制毒环境的清洁
So in terms of keeping our cook clean
和产品的纯正
and our product unadulterated,
我们必须严肃对待
we need to take this very seriously.
现在懂了吗
Now do you understand?
那这个就是你的砍蝇刀了
So is that your fly saber?
这是苍蝇拍
This is a swatter.
而且非常好用  谢谢
It happens to work quite well, thank you.
你的头怎么了
Uh-huh. Hey, what happened to your head?
没怎么  我很好
Nothing. I'm fine.
不是撞的吗  而且撞得很严重
You didn't hit it, like really... really hard?
我的头不是问题  杰西
My head is not the problem, Jesse.
苍蝇才是
The fly is the problem.
你不会是...试了我们的产品吧
You didn't happen to maybe... try our product, did you?
杰西  我知道对你这样的门外汉来说
Jess I know this seems unusual to you, a layman.
一只苍蝇...是无关紧要的  对吗
A fly... I get it... seems insignificant, right?
但是相信我
But trust me.
在实验室这种高度受控环境中
In a highly controlled environment such as this...
任何污染物
...any pollutant..
不管多么微小
...no matter how small...
都有可能彻底...
...could completely...
喂
Hello.
干嘛
What?
你整晚都在这吗
Were you here all night?
你睡过觉了吗
Have you even slept?
没  杰西  听着  我没事
No. Jesse, look. I'm fine. Okay
你能不能专心...
Will you just please focus...
好了  我们已经晚点了  赶紧开工
Okay, look. We're running late, so let's just get started.
好不好  早死早超生
Shall we? The sooner we do it, the sooner we're done.
他妈的  终于正常了
Frickin' finally.
你这是干嘛
What are you doing?
该加碱了
It's time to alkaline.
我说的你没听进去
Have you not heard a word I said?
没把这苍蝇搞死前  不制毒
No cooking until this fly is dealt with.
你当我刚才自言自语吗
Have I been speaking to myself?
喂  时间可不多了
The timer went off, yo.
你觉得这批货多久才能好  一两小时吗
How long is this batch going to be good for? An hour? Two?
除非清掉污染物  否则这批货是不会好的
The batch will be good for nothing if we don't clear the contaminant.
清掉污染物
Clear the contaminant?
我们制的是冰毒
We're making meth here,
又不是航天飞机
not space shuttles.
逮住那苍蝇之前  什么也不制
We're making nothing until we catch this fly.
什么苍蝇嘛
What fly?
这他妈哪有什么苍蝇嘛
Where the hell is this fly?
我看都没看见
Not like I've even seen the thing.
说不定你那啥正压力把它吹出门去了呢
Maybe your positive pressure blew it out the door or something.
不会的  它就在这附近  明白吗
No, no. It is here. It is around. Okay?
就在这  我不会允许这批货暴露在外
He's around, and am not going to expose this batch
被污染物影响  完毕
to the open air and contamination. Period.
你可以选择现在出去  让我自己搞定
Now, you can leave me to deal with this myself,
或者来帮我
or you can help me,
不过你说对了
but you are right.
我们的确快没时间了
We are running out of time,
请你现在就回答我
so I need your answer right now.
好吧
Okay.
你这是在浪费时间
Hey, tick-tock. Yo.
虽然我的确喜欢制纯正货  但现实点
Look, I like making cherry products, but let's keep it real.
瘾君子根本不在乎是否纯正
All right, we make poison for people who don't care.
他们可能是世上最不挑剔的顾客
We probably have the most unpicky customers in the world.
不  你少找借口
No, no, no, no, no. No rationalizing.
它随时可能出现  别放弃
We'll find it any minute now. Don't give up.
你知不知道...
Did you--
糖果制造的生产标准里有一条
Did you know that there's an acceptable level of rat turds
即可接受的老鼠粪便的程度
that can go into candy bars?
还是政府出台的  老兄
That's the government, Jack.
政府都不怎么关心产品质量
Even the government doesn't care that much about quality.
你知道热狗里都放些什么吗
You know what is okay to put in hotdogs? Huh?
猪唇跟猪屁眼
Pig lips and assholes,
要我说  混蛋  随便放
but I say, hey, have at it, bitchs,
老子就喜欢吃热狗
because I love hotdogs,
你看  我...
and, you know, see what I'm--
你在干什么
What are you doing?
没什么
Oh. Hey.
让我先把活干完
Look, let me just top it off,
很快就好  行不行
all right, really quick.
加点氢氧化钠[碱]  盖上盖子
A little sodium hydroxide, shut the lid,
没有污染  就完事了
no harm done. Then we're golden.
别动它  这是命令
It stays closed. That's an order.
你命令个屁  希特勒
You can't order shit, Adolf.
我们是平等的合伙人  还记得不
We're 50-50 partners. Remember?
天  你到底哪根筋不对
God, what is your problem, bro?
你他妈神经病
Freakin' psycho.
杰西
Jesse.
上帝  好像伤到骨头了
Oh, God, it, like, hit bone.
杰西
Jesse.
看到没有
You see it, right?
看到没
You see it?
看到了
Yeah.
干掉它
Get it.
你想让我去打它
You want me to get it?
没错
Yes.
等等  悠着点
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Slow.
缓慢移动
Move slowly.
我知道
I know.
我正缓慢移动
I'm moving slowly, yeah.
没错  苍蝇拍给我
Absolutely. I'm just going to need your swatter thing.
好的  给我
Yeah. Come on.
就这样  给我
Oh, yeah. It's okay, come on.
拜托  稳住了
Come on. Make it count.
好  不不  我要...
Yeah, no, no, I'm gonna--
我手头有准儿  放心
I'm going to make it count, all right.
好的  现在
Ok. Now.
我数到三
On three.
好的
Okay.
一
One--
爽了吗
Yeah. You like that?
疼吧
Hurts, huh?
你打到它没
Did you get it?
-我想是的  -它在哪里
- I think so, yeah. - Where is it?
我不知道  那无关紧要
I don't know. It doesn't matter.
谁在乎  我干掉它了
Who cares? I got it.
上帝  开什么玩笑吗
Oh, Jesus, seriously?
它在哪里
Where is it?
就在那里  看那里
It's, uh, right there. Look.
看到没  我就说我成功了
Look. See? I told you I got it.
这是葡萄干
This is a raisin.
我肯定打到它了
Look, I definitely got it, man.
好吧...
All right--
伙计
Oh, man.
它还挺厉害
He's got some skills, yo.
你把它练出来了
you give him that.
听着
Look...
尽管我觉得你不会明白
I feel like I'm running out of ways to explain this to you,
但我还想再说明一次
but once more I shall try.
这只苍蝇是当前头等大事
This fly is a major problem for us.
它会毁掉整批货物
It will ruin our batch.
只有灭了它
Now, we need to destroy it
把它留下的痕迹弄干净  才能继续制毒
and every trace of it so we can cook.
要是失败了...
Failing that...
我们就完蛋了
we're dead.
我们不能出差错
There is no more room for error.
这帮人是容不得差错的
Not with these people.
出去透透气怎么样
All right, how about we go get some air?
出去透透气
Get some air?
这就是你对"我们问题大条了"的反应吗
Your answer to "We're sliding head-first into a massive crap--"
怀特老师
Mister-- Mr. White,
我明白那只苍蝇的重要性
I understand that the fly is a serious thing.
我是完全赞同你的
Now, all right? I'm on board.
我是说  出去透透气
I'm just saying maybe if we went and got some air,
或许能想到办法抓住它
it would help us come up with a plan on how to catch it.
然后再回来
Then come back down here
干掉它
and subtract his ass.
等等  你带钥匙了吗
Oh, wait, do you have your keys?
-带了  -你确定吗
- Yeah. - You're sure?
要被锁外面就惨了
Last thing we need is to get locked out.
带了
Yeah.
如果你不肯帮我  就滚远点
If you're not going to help me, stay out of my way!
有人有斧头吗
Yo. Yo, does somebody have an ax I can use?
斧头之类的
El ax-o!
危险的斧头
Peligroso! El ax-o!
主断电器  危险  440伏特电压
终于找到你了
There we go.
晚安吧
Say good night.
我操
Son of a bitch!
操
Son of a...
妈的  见鬼
Shit! Damn it!
他妈的怎么回事...
Where in the hell is that...
怎么回事
What the hell?
要来杯饮料吗
Need some juice maybe?
不客气
Knock yourself out.
这才是真的  你那个不管用
It's a real one. Yeah, like yours was working.
不  不
No, no...
没用  听着  我们是要净化实验室
No, no-- Look, we're trying to decontaminate.
越弄越脏可不是净化
You don't decontaminate by contaminating further.
这都是些什么破玩意儿
What the hell is all this?
这个怎么样
Here, how about this?
无毒胶水带
"Nontoxic glue strips."
它能散发信息素
Yeah, baby, it's got pheromones, all right.
我买了很多  可以把这地方挂满
I got a buttload. We hang them up all over the place.
它插翅难飞
It won't be able to resist.
希望贴的够多
I sure hope we have enough.
我敢打包票  绝对够多了
I'm going to go out on a limb and say yeah.
你看到它没
Do you see him?
你有多久没睡觉了
How long do you think you've been awake?
干嘛一直问我这个
Why do you keep asking me that?
我寻思着你可以喝点咖啡
Just figure you could use some coffee, is all.
我得来点
I know I could.
怎么样
How about it?
好的
Yeah.
要牛奶和方糖吗
You take cream and sugar?
清咖啡就好
Black is fine.
随它去吧
Why don't you just leave him be?
让它自投罗网
Let the traps do the work.
信息素会管用的
These pheromones are supposed to kick ass.
随时都可能逮住这小杂种
I bet we catch this mo-fo any second.
谢谢
Thank you.
你有没有在家中与野生动物纠缠的经历
You ever have, like, a wild animal trapped in your house?
印象中没有
Not that I can recall, no.
我遇到过一次
We did, this one time,
在我姨妈家的时候
back when it was my aunt's house,
在她死于癌症之前
back before she died of cancer.
负鼠  又大又丑
Possum. Big, freaky-looking bitch.
从什么时候起
Hey, since when did they
它们更名为袋鼫  原名有什么问题
change it to "Opossum"? What's up with that?
在我小时候
I mean, when I was coming up,
它就叫负鼠
it was just "Possum."
袋鼫听起来像是爱尔兰那边的
"Opossum" makes it sound like he's Irish or something.
为什么把一切改来改去的
Why they gotta go changing everything?
不管怎样  只是肥老鼠罢了
Whatever. They're just big rats anyways,
长着粉红色尾巴和脸的老鼠
giant pink-tailed rats with their pink rat faces,
丑的要死
totally freaky,
像外星鼠
like alien rats.
实际上  它不是困在房子里
Actually, it's not so much that he got trapped,
它就住在房子底下
but he was living there, you know, under the house.
你能听到它到各房间串门
You could hear him going from, like, room to room,
跑的飞快
always scurrying around.
有时晚上还能看到它们出来
Sometimes I'd see him outside at night,
它就假装一动不动
and he would just, you know, freeze.
好像这样你就看不到它了
And it's like you're not looking right at it. Right?
它感觉自己能愚弄你
I mean, it thinks it's fooling you.
它们就这点花招  喜欢装死
That's what they do, honestly. They play dead or whatever.
太傻了
It's just so lame.
这故事有重点吗
Is there a discernible point to this story,
或是你在不久的将来才表达的出来的重点
a point that you'll be arriving at sometime in the near future?
就是让我记忆深刻  忘不掉
It was just a total bitch to get out. It took forever.
叫了个人来  布置好陷阱
A guy came, set all these traps and all,
最后抓到了它
and he finally got it,
但我姨妈根本不信
but my aunt, she didn't believe it.
她坚持说还能听到它跑动的声音
She kept insisting she could still hear the thing.
抓没抓到根本没区别
I mean, you could not tell her any different.
她开始在椅子边上放了把旧伞
She started keeping an old umbrella by her chair.
她开始戳地板  冲它喊话
Man, she would just bang on the floor and yell at it,
还给它起了个名字
even gave it a name.
好像是...
It was, uh, Sc--
斯克莱博
Scrabble.
没错  就这么叫的
Yeah, that was it.
斯克莱博  别吵了  咚咚咚
"Scrabble, just knock it off." Bang, bang, bang.
直到去世  她一直这样
She got like that toward the end.
像入了迷似的
Got obsessive about stuff,
简直走火入魔了
just got mad about stuff.
我们不知道是怎么回事
We didn't know what was up.
根本不像她的处事作风
It wasn't like her to be that way.
结果是...
But it turned out that the--
她的癌细胞扩散到了脑部
the cancer had spread to her brain,
这才是原因
and that was why.
病灶转移了
It metastasized.
但幸好
But it was good that that
我们当时决定带她去看医生
was when we decided to take her to the doctor
然后了解到了她的情况
because then we knew what was up
并且让她接受了治疗
and got her some treatment
服了些药  让她不至于整天神经兮兮的
and meds so she wasn't stressing all the time.
之后她就好多了
It was a lot better after that.
她自己也开心多了
She was a lot happier.
那只该死的苍蝇跑哪儿去了
Where the hell is he?
我上礼拜才和我的肿瘤医生见了面
I've been to my oncologist, Jesse, just last week.
我的病情依然在缓解
I'm still in remission.
很健康
I'm healthy.
那很好
Okay, so good. Great.
是啊  没完没了的
Well, no end in sight.
也很好啊
That's great.
我找不着那苍蝇了
Well, I missed it.
曾经有些完美的时刻
There was some perfect moment,
都与我擦肩而过
and it passed me right by.
我当时得留下足够的钱给他们
Yeah, I had to have enough to leave them.
这才是最重要的
That was the whole point.
如果我当时没钱的话  这一切无意义了
None of this makes any sense if I didn't have enough.
但那得是在斯凯勒发现之前
But it had to be before she found out... Skyler.
一定得在那之前
It had to be before that.
那个完美的时刻
Perfect moment...
什么的时刻
For what?
死亡时刻吗
To drop dead?
你是说你想死吗
What, are you saying you want to die?
我是说我活得太长了
I'm saying I've lived too long.
我想让他们想念我
You want them to actually miss you.
你明白吗
You know?
想让他们对我的回忆
You want their memories of you
就好像...
to be--
但她就是不...
But she just won't
她就是不明白
She just won't understand.
不管我的解释有多么合情合理
No matter how well I explain it,
那段时间她就是...
these days she just has this--
就是...
this--
我真的觉得  有那么一些话...
I mean, I truly believe there exists some combination of words.
肯定有...
There must exist
那么些话
certain words
特殊而又明确的话  来解释这一切
in a certain, specific order that would explain all of this,
但在她面前  我就怎么也想不出来
but with her I just-- I just can't ever seem to find them.
怀特老师  要不您先坐会儿
Mr. White, how about you just sit down?
我觉得是在我那次神游之前...
I was thinking maybe before the fugue state,
但在那之前
but before the fugue state
我的钱还没有凑够
they didn't have enough money,
所以不是那时候
so no, not then.
而且那会儿我女儿还没出世
And plus my daughter wasn't born yet.
所以一定得在霍莉出生之后才行
It had to be after Holly was born.
怀特老师
Mr. White--
肯定也得在我做手术之前
Definitely before the surgery.
天啊
Oh, Christ.
该死的手机二号
That damn second cell phone.
我怎么可能会...
I mean how could I possibly...
我知道了
Ah, I know the moment.
应该是珍妮死的那个晚上
It was the night Jane died.
我当时在家  家里尿布用完了
I was at home and we needed diapers,
所以我说我去买
and so I said I'd go,
但那只是个借口
but it was just an excuse.
实际上  那晚
Actually, that was the night I--
我去给你送钱去了  记得吗
I brought you your money, remember?
恩  记得
Yeah, I remember.
但那之后  我去了家酒吧
But afterward I stopped at a bar.
太奇怪了  我从没一个人去过酒吧
It was odd. I never do that, go to a bar alone.
我走了进去  坐了下来
I just walked in, sat down.
我一直没跟你提过
I never told you.
提什么  你去了间酒吧吗
That you went to a bar?
我坐下后  有个男人  一个陌生人
I sit down, and this man, this stranger,
他过来我和搭话
he engages me in conversation.
完全是个陌生人
He's a complete stranger.
但后来我发现  他是珍妮的父亲
But he turns out to be Jane's father,
唐纳德·马戈利斯
Donald Margolis.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我当时并不认识他
Of course I didn't know it at the time.
我以为只是个在酒吧喝酒的人
I mean, it was just some guy in a bar.
直到坠机事件之后  新闻里到处
Didn't put it together until after the crash
都在报道他的时候  我才想起来
when he was all over the news.
珍妮的父亲
Jane's dad.
你想下这几率有多小
I mean, think of the odds.
我试着去算了下
Once I tried to calculate them,
但是太复杂了
but they're astronomical.
想想看这几率
I mean, think of the odds
恰好是我  恰好是那晚  恰好那酒吧
of me going in, sitting down
恰好坐那男人的旁边
that night in that bar next to that man.
你们聊什么了
What did you talk about?
火星上的水源
Oh, water on Mars.
家庭
Family.
关于家庭的都聊了什么
What about family?
我告诉他我有个女儿
I told him that I had a daughter,
他说他也有一个
and he told me he had one, too.
然后他说  永远不要放弃家人
Then he said, "Never give up on family."
所以我听他的了  没有放弃家人
And I didn't. I-- I took his advice.
宇宙是随机的
The universe is random.
可变的
It's not inevitable.
是混乱的
It's simple chaos.
是无休止的  无序的  亚原子粒子间的碰撞
It's subatomic particles in endless, aimless collision.
这是科学教予我们的
That's what science teaches us,
但这又是什么意思呢
but what is this saying?
就恰巧在那一晚
What is it telling us,
和我喝酒的那个人的女儿死了
when on the very night that this man's daughter dies,
这是想告诉我们什么呢
it's me who's having a drink with him?
这怎么会是随机的呢
How can that be random?
坐下来吧
Hey, sit down.
不  不
No-- No.
不坐
No, it's--
不  就是那个时刻
No, that-- that was the moment.
那天晚上
That night.
我不该离开家
I should never have left home.
不该去你家
Never gone to your house.
这样事情也许会...
Maybe things would have--
我以为我...
Oh, thought I was--
在家看电视
I was at home watching TV.
看些
Some--
看些关于大象的自然节目
Some nature program about elephants.
斯凯勒和霍莉在另外一间房
Skyler and Holly were in another room.
我可以从婴儿监视器里听到她们的声音
I could hear them on the baby monitor.
我听到她在唱摇篮曲
She was singing a lullaby.
如果能停在那一刻
If had just lived right up to that moment
就在那一刻
and not one second more--
...将是多么完美
...that would've been perfect.
它不会下来了
He's not coming down.
上面肯定跟泰国一样热
Must be Thailand-hot up there.
所以它喜欢那
That's why he likes it.
泰国很热对吧
Thailand's hot, right?
嗯
Yeah.
我就知道
See? That's why.
天
Oh, Jesus.
等等
Hey, wait.
坐这儿
Here.
它不会下来了
He's not coming down.
它要在那儿待一辈子
He's staying up there forever.
你在  你在干嘛
What are you-- What are you doing?
你以为呢  我要去干了它
What do you think? I'm going to get that bitch.
不行  你会摔断脖子的
No, you're going to break your neck.
是啊  是啊
Yeah, yeah. Just--
我说真的呢  这可不是个好主意
No, seriously, you're-- This is a bad idea.
该死
Damn it.
杰西
Jesse.
帮我扶稳就好了
Just hold onto it.
扶稳了吗
Hold it still?
杰西
Jesse.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
抱什么歉
Sorry for what?
因为你突然发疯吗
Being a lunatic?
珍妮的事  我很抱歉
I'm sorry about Jane.
我也很抱歉
Yeah. Me, too.
不  我是说...
No, I mean, uh--
我非常抱歉
I'm very sorry.
那不是你的错
It's not your fault.
也不是我的错
But it's not mine either.
更不是她的错  谁都没错
It's no one's fault, not even hers.
本性难移你知道吗  怀特老师
We are who we are, Mr. White.
我俩就是瘾君子  有了钱又怎样
You know, just two junkies with a duffel bag full of cash.
还不是像你说的  活不过一个礼拜
Like you said, we both would've been dead within a week.
但我还是很想念她
But I miss her, though.
真的很想她
God, I do.
杰西  下来吧
Jesse, come down.
等等  就差那么一点点
Wait, I am so close.
别管它了
Let it go.
我们得开始制毒了
We need to cook.
那这"污染物"怎么办
What about the contamination?
反正都已经污染了
It's all contaminated.
我应该是吓到它了
I definitely scared him.
它应该不会再回来了
Probably stay out of our way--
死  终于干死你了
Zap! Somebody got got, yo!
你看到了吗
You see that, Mister--
都包好了吗
Bins are packed?
包好了
Bins are packed.
产量如何
How's the yield?
202磅  有点零头
Two-oh-two and change.
你一个人回家没事吧
You okay getting home?
嗯  我好多了
Yeah. Better.
谢谢
Thanks.
那么  日安
Ma?ana, then.
杰西  过来一下
Jesse, come here.
我刚在里面不好说
I couldn't chance saying it inside.
因为里面可能被监视着
For all I know, the lab's wired for sound.
我们之前提到的那半磅
That half a pound that I said we're off by--
我不是想责怪你什么  但如果...
Now, I'm not accusing you, but if...
你明白的
You understand?
如果他们发现了...
And if they ever found out--
我才不鸟他们
I didn't take shit.
我只是说  我可能就没法保护你了
I'm just saying that I won't be able to protect you.
谁让你保护了
Who's asking you to?